* Specialized

* Explore

* [](javascript:void(0);;)

### RECOMMENDED

### RECENT SEARCHES[CLEAR](javascript:;)

### Please Change Your Browser

Internet Explorer is no longer supported. It is recommended to use other browsers.

Continue Viewing

DJI Privacy Policy
------------------

DJI Privacy Policy
==================

General
-------

Last Updated: July 1, 2023  
  
Thank you for your interest in SZ DJI Technology Co., Ltd. and its affiliated companies (“DJI”, “we”, or “us”) and in the various hardware, firmware, software, websites, applications, and services provided by us and on which a link to this Privacy Policy (this “Policy”) is displayed (each, a “Product” or “Service” and, collectively, the “DJI Products and Services”).  
  
This Policy describes:

* The information that we gather from you,
    
* How we use and share this information,
    
* The rights and choices you have regarding this information,
    
* The steps we take to protect this information,
    
* The information gathered by third-party services,
    
* How we transfer your information,
    
* How we may change this Policy, and
    
* How you may contact us.

By using DJI Products and Services, you consent to the privacy practices described in this Policy. This Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the Terms of Use for the DJI Products and Services you use.  
  
If you are a California resident, please also review our California Privacy Notice for more information about the types of personal information we collect and disclose, as well as how to exercise your rights under California law.  
  
For Dutch version of privacy policy, please refer to [DJI privacybeleid](https://terra-1-g.djicdn.com/851d20f7b9f64838a34cd02351370894/legal/Clean%20DJI%20-%20Privacy%20Policy%20_NL-NL.pdf)

Information We Collect
----------------------

We may collect information about you directly from you, from third parties, and automatically through your use of the DJI Products and Services. Some information we collect from you are referred to as “personal information” or “personal data” in this Policy. Personal information or personal data is data that can identify you, or data that we can relate to you, such as your name, email address, credit card number, and shipping address.  
  
If you do not provide your information when requested, you may not be able to use DJI Products and Services if that information is necessary to provide you with DJI Products and Services or if we are legally required to collect it.  

* Account Information. When you create a DJI account, you may provide us with information that includes your user ID, email address (or phone number, based on the country located), password or other information for account verification. You might choose to provide us with additional information — like gender, birthday, professional information and other information on your profile page.
    
* Contact Information. When you place an order with DJI, sign up for notifications or updates, or contact us for customer service, you may provide us with your contact information including your name, alias, email address, shipping address, billing address and phone number(s). Certain jurisdictions require provision of contact information when activating unmanned aerial system (UAS) products, opening online accounts, or under other similar circumstances as required by law. DJI only collects and stores UAS-regulatory related information to the extent required by applicable law.
    
* Payment Information. When you place an order with DJI or engage in financial transactions by using DJI Products and Services, you may provide us with your payment information such as your bank account, credit card number, or debit card number.
    
* Photos and Videos. DJI does not automatically collect your photo or video without your consent and affirmative actions. When you choose to upload your photos, videos or other content using DJI Products and Services, including text content relating thereto, we may collect and store such content, including EXIF data relating to the photo or video. If such content contains information about others, you should obtain any required or appropriate consent from such persons and inform them about this Policy prior to uploading such content to DJI.
    
* Communications. When you contact us, we may collect information about your communications with us, including your contact information, and the time, topic, and content of your communications.
    
* Location Information. When you activate DJI hardware products, use the map function of our apps, synchronize your flight record, obtain UAS safety/regulatory notifications, share your content on Skypixel, or search for nearby flying spots, you may provide us with geolocation information. In order to provide your location, you may be required to enable certain features of your device (such as GPS, Wi-Fi, and Bluetooth) to identify your location through a variety of means, including GPS location, IP address, cell tower location, or detection by physical on-location Wi-Fi or Bluetooth sensors. If your location is collected through Wi-Fi or Bluetooth sensors of your mobile device or other non-DJI Products, please be aware that such sensors, and the associated data services, may be provided by a third party, which may access such information for the purpose of providing such data services to DJI. You may provide your geolocation information to third-party map service providers to receive location-based services on DJI Products. When you unlock the geofencing features embedded in DJI Products and Services, you may provide us with the area code of your unlocked areas (“Authorization Zones”).
    
* Device-Related and Flight-Related Information. When you activate DJI products, request for after-sales service, unlock the geofencing features or upgrade the firmware, you may provide us with information about your DJI device, including model and serial number. Our after-sales team may ask for your flight data to provide the service you requested.
    
* Technical Information. When you visit our webpage or use our mobile applications, you may provide us with technical information about the device running the browser or the application. Such information includes your IP address or device address, web browser and/or device type, the web pages or sites that you visit just before or just after you use a Product or Service, hardware version, and operating system. We also may use these technologies to collect information regarding your interaction with DJI email messages, such as whether you opened, clicked on, or forwarded a message.
    
* Employment-related Information. When you apply for a position at DJI, you may provide us with your educational information, such as your academic degree and graduated school, and employment-related information, such as your former employers and working achievements. We may also collect such information from third party recruiters or websites.
    
* Cookies. We use cookies and other similar technologies (e.g. pixels etc.) on DJI websites and online services. Cookies are used to collect information, including personal data, from you. Cookies are small files which, when placed on your device, enable us to provide certain features and functionality. To learn more about cookies please see our Cookie Policy.

How We Use the Information We Collect
-------------------------------------

We use information we collect through DJI Products and Services in a variety of ways in providing the DJI Products and Services and operating our business. The use of information that we collect includes the following:

* To operate and provide features of the DJI Products and Services, to verify and manage DJI user accounts, to provide services and information that you request, and to process and deliver entries and rewards in connection with promotions that may be offered from time to time by DJI. We will process your personal data in accordance with this Policy and any of your preferences, which are expressed via DJI Products and Services, including SkyPixel and the DJI Fly App. We may use any of the categories of personal information described above for this purpose.
    
* To personalize the content you receive and provide you with tailored content that will be of interest to you. We may use your Account Information and Device-Related Information for this purpose.
    
* To understand and analyze the usage trends and preferences, to improve the DJI Products and Services, and to develop new products, services, features, and functionality. We may use your Technical Information for this purpose.
    
* To contact you for administrative and informational purposes, including for customer service. We may send direct marketing such as communications, including updates on promotions and events, relating to products and services offered by us and by third parties we work with. If you are an individual or consumer we will only send you direct marketing with your consent or as permitted by applicable law. You may send unsubscribe requests or withdraw your consent at any time. Please visit the section Your Rights and Choices Regarding Collected Information to find out more. We may use your Account Information and Contact Information for this purpose.
    
* To detect, prevent, and respond to fraud, abuse, security risks, and technical issues that could harm our users, us, or the public. We may use your Account Information, Device-Related and Flight-Related Information for this purpose.
    
* For any other purposes disclosed to you at the time we collect your information or pursuant to your consent. We may use any of the categories of personal information described above for this purpose.
    
* We will aggregate personal data we collect, such as the number and frequency of your visits to our sites and apps, to produce metrics and statistical information. We use aggregate data to help us understand how the site is being used and to improve its usability. We also use it to enhance the quality and availability of products and services we offer. We may use your Technical Information for this purpose.
    
* To comply with applicable laws, such as laws related to the use of unmanned aerial system (UAS) products or opening online accounts. We may use your Account Information and Device-Related Information for this purpose.  
      
    If you are located in the European Economic Area, we will only use your information when we have a valid legal ground, including when:
    
* You have consented to the use of your information, for example to send you marketing communications.
    
* We need to use your information to enter into or perform a contract with you, for example to deliver DJI products, to provide map services, or provide you with the customer support and other after-sales services.
    
* We need to use your information to comply with a legal obligation, for example to comply with a court order, subpoena, or warrant.
    
* We or a third party have a legitimate interest in using your information. In particular, we have a legitimate interest in using your information to understand and improve our DJI Products and Services, and to monitor for and prevent fraud. We only rely on our own or a third party’s legitimate interests to process your information when these interests are not overridden by your rights and interests.

We do not use profiling to make decisions that would significantly affect you.

When We Disclose Information
----------------------------

We will not disclose your information that we collect through DJI Products and Services to third parties except as described in this Policy or as we disclose to you at the time the information is collected. We may disclose the categories of information described above in “Information We Collect” to the third parties and for the purposes described below:  

* We may disclose your information to our parent company, affiliates and subsidiaries globally when permitted by law, and necessary to provide you with DJI Products and Services. This information may include all of the categories described above in “Information We Collect.”
    
* Any information that you voluntarily choose to make publicly available by uploading it to a publicly accessible site or venue using DJI Products and Services (including sharing information on SkyPixel or on DJI’s online community forum, the “DJI Forum”), or that you otherwise elect to make public, will be available to anyone who has access to that content, including other users. The categories of information disclosed here may include: Photos and Video.
    
* We work with third party service providers to provide payment facilitation, parcel transportation, application development, traffic monitoring or analysis, electronic messaging, and other services for us. We require these service providers to use or disclose the information they process on our behalf, only as necessary to perform services on our behalf or comply with legal requirements. This information may include all of the categories described above in “Information We Collect.”
    
* According to local laws and regulations, such as Remote Identification or other aviation regulations and requirements, your device-related information, product location, and remote controller (ground control station) location may be transmitted to and received by individuals, companies, or organizations determined by aviation regulations to be appropriate receivers of such information. Please refer to your local authorities for more information regarding what types of your information are subject to these requirements. Your DJI aircraft device information, such as serial number, product location, remote controller (ground control station) location, and device model may be locally broadcast and received by DJI’s AeroScope Remote Identification feature to promote flight safety near critical infrastructure, airports, special events, or to support the activities of law enforcement and security agencies. DJI’s qualified AeroScope dealers are only authorized to sell AeroScope receivers to government agencies involved in public safety, security, or law enforcement, aviation safety researchers, or to owners and operators of critical facilities such as airports, power plants, and prisons.
    
* We may preserve and disclose your information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with applicable laws, in response to a court order, judicial or other government subpoena, warrant or enforceable request. This information may include all of the categories described above in “Information We Collect.”
    
* We also reserve the right to preserve and disclose your information that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to (i) take precautions against liability, (ii) protect ourselves or others from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses or activities, (iii) investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations, (iv) protect the security or integrity of the DJI Products and Services and any facilities or equipment used to make the DJI Products and Services available, or (v) protect our property or other legal rights (including, but not limited to, enforcement of our agreements), or the rights, property, or safety of others.This information may include all of the categories described above in “Information We Collect.”
    
* Information about our users, including information you provided and any information collected through DJI Products and Services, may be disclosed and otherwise communicated to an acquirer, successor, or assignee as part of any merger, acquisition, debt financing, sale of assets, or similar transaction, or in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership in which information is transferred to one or more third parties as one of our business assets. This information may include all of the categories described above in “Information We Collect.”
    
* We may make certain aggregated, de-identified, or non-identifying information about users of DJI Products and Services available to third parties for various purposes, including (i) compliance with various reporting obligations; (ii) for business or marketing purposes; (iii) product safety analysis; or (iv) to assist such parties in understanding our users’ interests, habits, and usage patterns for certain programs, content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality of DJI Products and Services.  
      
    We do not sell your personal data as “sale” is defined in applicable state laws in the U.S.. We also does not “share” your personal data as that term is defined in California Law.

Your Rights and Choices Regarding Collected Information
-------------------------------------------------------

You may update, correct, or delete certain DJI account information and preferences by accessing your account preferences page, available through certain DJI Products and Services, including the DJI.com and SkyPixel websites and various mobile applications. If you receive commercial email or text messages from us, you may unsubscribe at any time by following the instructions contained within the email or text message. You may also opt out from receiving commercial email or text messages from us or object to be profiled by sending your request to us by email at [support@privacy.dji.com](mailto:support@privacy.dji.com).  
  
If you are located in the European Economic Area, you may also have the right to request access to additional information, including the right to request access to and receive certain information we maintain about you; to update or correct inaccuracies in the information we maintain about you; to receive a copy of the information which you provided for its transmission to another company; to object to the processing on grounds relating to your particular situation; and to have the information blocked, deleted, or erased, as appropriate. When we process personal data on the basis of your consent, you can also withdraw your consent. If you withdraw your consent, we will apply your preferences going forward, and this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before you withdrew your consent.  
  
If you are a U.S. resident, depending on your state of residency, such as California and Colorado, you may also exercise certain rights by contacting us using the details provided in the “Our Contact Information” section below. You may make a request to exercise the following rights with respect to your personal data (as defined in the privacy law applicable to your state of residence):  
  
• To confirm whether or not DJI processes your personal data and request access to such data;  
• To delete personal data you have provided to DJI and personal data obtained about you from sources other than DJI;  
• To correct inaccuracies in your personal data;  
• To opt out of the processing of your personal data for purposes of: (i) targeted advertising; (ii) the sale of personal data; and (iii) profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects. Please note that we do not engage in such sale, targeted advertising or profiling;  
• To obtain a copy of your personal data in a portable and, to the extent technically feasible, readily usable format; and  
• To appeal any decision with regard to your privacy request by contacting us here or using the details provided in the “Our Contact Information” section below.  
  
Note, however, that if you exercise your right to object or your rights of blocking, deletion or to be “forgotten” or if you decline to share certain information with us, or if you withdraw your consent to our processing of information about you, we may not be able to provide to you some, or any, of the features and functionality of DJI Products and Services.  
  
Likewise, if you close your DJI account, you will not be able to sign in to DJI Products or Services or access any of your information. However, you can open a new account at any time. Please note that while any changes you make will be reflected in active user databases within a reasonable period of time, we may retain all information you submit, as authorized under applicable law, for backups, archiving, prevention of fraud and abuse, analytics, satisfaction of legal obligations, or where we otherwise reasonably believe that we have a legitimate reason to do so. In addition, if certain information has already been provided to third parties as described in this Policy, retention of that information will be subject to those third parties’ policies.  
  
If you wish to exercise any rights you have under applicable data protection law, including the right to access, amend or delete any information we hold about you, you may contact us at [support@privacy.dji.com](mailto:support@privacy.dji.com).  
  
We will review any information you provide with your request and may request additional information to ensure we are interacting with the correct individual. If you have an online account with us, you may be required to log-in to your account for identity verification. If you do not have an account with us, additional information to verify your identity may be required by law before we may take action upon such a request. This additional information may vary depending on the nature of your request and/or the nature of the information about which your request relates. In some cases, we may also be required by law to obtain a signed declaration under penalty of perjury from you that you are the subject of the request being made. If we suspect fraudulent or malicious activity on or from your account, we will delay taking action on your request until we can appropriately verify your identity and the request as authentic.  
  
You may designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf pursuant to applicable law. We accept documentation of your designation in the form of a valid power of attorney and/or a notarized statement. You must submit evidence of your designation of an authorized agent in writing to: SZ DJI Technology Co., Ltd.14th Floor, West Wing, Skyworth Semiconductor Design Building, No.18 Gaoxin South 4th Ave, Nanshan District, Shenzhen, China, 518057. We may require verification of your authorized agent in addition to the information for verification above.

Third-Party Services
--------------------

DJI Products and Services may contain features or links to websites and services provided by third parties. Any information you choose to provide on third-party sites or services, or any information otherwise collected by such third-party sites or services is collected directly by the operators of such services and is subject to those operators’ policies, if any, governing privacy and security, even if accessed through DJI Products and Services.  
  
We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of third-party sites or services to which links or access are provided through DJI Products and Services. If you opt in to use such third-party services, please be sure to check the Privacy Policies of these sites as well as their “Terms of Use” before engaging in any business or uploading any information.

Children’s Privacy
------------------

Except for certain products that are marked as “14+” or “for customers over the age of 14”, DJI Products and Services are not directed to children under the age of 16. We do not knowingly collect or process information from children under the age of 16 without obtaining parental consent.

Data Security
-------------

We use certain physical, organizational, and technical safeguards that are designed to improve the integrity and security of information that we collect and maintain. Please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable and thus we cannot and do not guarantee that your information will not be accessed, viewed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or organizational safeguards.

International Transfers of Personal Data
----------------------------------------

Your information collected by DJI may be transferred to and accessed by DJI entities and business partners globally to provide DJI Products and Services to you. If you choose to use DJI Products and Services from the European Economic Area (EEA), then DJI GmbH in Germany is the data controller, and we may transfer your personal data outside of EEA for storage and processing. You should be aware that the local laws in non-EEA countries may provide less protection than the laws applicable in the EEA. We nonetheless provide the same level of protection as specified in this Policy, regardless of the location of processing. For international transfer of data collected in the EEA, we require data recipients to enter into the standard contractual clauses approved by the European Commission. You may obtain a copy of the standard contractual clauses by contacting us at [support@privacy.dji.com](mailto:support@privacy.dji.com).

Retention of Your Information
-----------------------------

We retain your information to provide service to you, or as required by applicable laws or regulations. We aim to retain your information only for the period necessary to fulfil our obligations under this Policy, unless otherwise required or permitted by law. We will carefully assess the need to collect data, the type of data collected, relevant legal framework, and the statute of limitations when determining the retention period.

Changes and Updates to this Policy
----------------------------------

We may update this Policy from time to time. If we modify this Policy, we will make it available on or through the DJI Products and Services and indicate the date of the latest revision. We will make reasonable efforts to notify you of the change.

Our Contact Information
-----------------------

Please contact us with any questions or comments about this Policy or our data practices by email at [support@privacy.dji.com](mailto:support@privacy.dji.com) or in writing to SZ DJI Technology Co., Ltd.14th Floor, West Wing, Skyworth Semiconductor Design Building, No.18 Gaoxin South 4th Ave, Nanshan District, Shenzhen, China, 518057. If you are located in the European Economic Area, then unless otherwise indicated in this Policy, the entity responsible for the collection, use, and processing of your information described in this Policy is DJI GmbH, located at Industriestr. 12, 97618 Niederlauer, Germany. You may contact us to have your information blocked, deleted or erased, or to opt out from profiling where your prior usage of DJI Products and Services is processed to provide you with customized or personalized products, services or advertisements, or to obtain copies of certain of your information in a portable format. If you think that any of your rights have been infringed by us, you may also lodge a complaint with us or with a data protection regulator, including in your country of residence, place of work or where an incident took place. You can find out more information about your rights by contacting your local data protection regulator or the Bavaria State Office for Data Protection Supervision, or by searching their website at [https://www.lda.bayern.de/en/index.html](https://www.lda.bayern.de/en/index.html). If you have any queries or wish to exercise any of your rights under this Policy, please contact us as set out above.

Cookie Policy
-------------

### What are Cookies?

When you use DJI websites or online services, we may send one or more cookies — small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters — to your device. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Service. Please review your web browser “Help” file to learn the proper way to modify your cookie settings. Please note that if you delete or choose not to accept certain types of cookies, you may not be able to utilize the features of DJI Products and Services to their fullest potential. We may use third party cookies as well. For instance, we use Google Analytics to collect and process certain analytics data (Please refer to [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners) for additional privacy options, if any). DJI does not process or respond to web browsers’ “do not track” signals or other similar transmissions that indicate a request to disable online tracking of users who use DJI Products and Services.  
  
We may also automatically record certain information from your device by using various types of technology, including “clear gifs” or “web beacons” (together with cookies, “cookies and similar technologies”). This automatically collected information may include your IP address or other device address or ID, web browser and/or device type, the web pages or sites that you visit just before or just after you use a Product or Service, the pages or other content you view or otherwise interact with on a Product or Service, and the dates and times that you visit, access, or use DJI Products and Services. We also may use these technologies to collect information regarding your interaction with email messages, such as whether you opened, clicked on, or forwarded a message.

### Cookies Used by DJI

We use different types of cookies as listed below. They help us to provide and improve the DJI Products and Services, such as showing you the most relevant information and your customized webpage. Some or all of the cookies listed may be stored in your browser or devices.  
  
Strictly necessary cookies. These cookies are essential for you to use the DJI Products and Services, such as the cookies used for carrying out the transmission of a communication, the cookies that record requests for information from the Internet and block web attacks so as to ensure web security, the cookies that are strictly necessary for us to provide information society services that you request. You must accept strictly necessary cookies to be able to use DJI Products and Services.  
  
Preference cookies. These cookies are also known as “functionality cookies”, these cookies allow us to remember choices you have made through your use of the DJI Products and Services, like what language you prefer, what region you are in, or what your username and password are so you can automatically log in. These cookies can help us reallocate work load among our servers and enable our webpages to respond faster.  
  
Statistics cookies. These cookies are also known as “performance cookies”, these cookies collect information about how you use the DJI Products and Services, like which webpages you visited and which links you clicked on. These cookies can help us to improve user experience of using DJI Products and Services.  
  
Marketing cookies. These cookies can track your online activities to help us deliver more relevant advertisements or limit the number of time that the same advertisement is shown to you.

### Manage Your Cookie Settings

DJI offers you the possibility to set your preferences regarding cookies. By clicking “Cookie Preferences” on the bottom of each webpage, you can select the types of Cookies our websites or online services use. You can change your preferences at any time; you can also withdraw the consent you have previously given to us.

### Cookies Use when You Use Mobile Devices

Some mobile devices share the same features with computers, such as the support of full-featured browsers. When you are using this type of devices such as smartphones, we use cookies in a similar way to when you are using computers. Other devices may use different technologies, such as local storage, Software Development Kits (SDKs), or Advanced Programming Interfaces (APIs) to facilitate aforementioned processes effectuated by cookies.  
  
We may obtain or receive information about your device, our apps, or other apps. We may also use these technologies to store information on your device. For example, we may receive information about the make and model of your mobile device when you are asking others for help through our app.

### Read of Particular Cookies

Browsers will send cookies for a particular domain (such as dji.com) to the website each time a device with those cookies accesses content from that domain. This means if your device stores cookies for dji.com, it will send those cookies to DJI when it accesses a webpage at dji.com.

### Cookie Use Without a DJI Account or After Your Logout

We still use cookies if you do not have a DJI account or have logged out your account. After your logout, we will use cookies to:

* Identify and terminate accounts in violation of the Terms of Use or DJI policies;
    
* Recover your lost account;
    
* Recognize use of public computers and notify you to reduce your risk of data theft;
    
* Understand your interaction with our Products and Services, and those of our partners.

If you do not have DJI account and have visited dji.com, we will use cookies to protect DJI Products and Services, and DJI customers from malicious activity such as denial-of-service attacks and mass creation of fake accounts.

California Privacy Notice
-------------------------

Last Updated or Reviewed: July 1, 2023  
  
This California Privacy Notice supplements the information and disclosures contained in our Privacy Policy. It applies to the Personal Information of certain California residents, who are Consumers receiving products or services for which we are a Business, as those terms are defined under the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (California Civil Code §§ 1798.100 to 1798.199) and its implementing regulations, as amended or superseded from time to time (the “CCPA”), .  
  
Any capitalized terms herein are intended to have the same meaning as in the CCPA.

### California Consumers’ Rights and Choices

If you are a Consumer, California law may permit you to request information regarding the:

* Categories of Personal Information (as defined by applicable California law) collected, Sold, Shared or disclosed by us;
    
* Purposes for which categories of Personal Information collected by us are used;
    
* Sources of information from which we collect Personal Information;
    
* The categories of third parties to whom we disclosed Personal Information; and
    
* Specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about you.

In addition, if you are a Consumer you may

* Opt-out of Sale or Sharing of your Personal Information for cross-context behavioral advertising purposes. We do not sell or share your Personal Information as those terms are defined under California law;
    
* Opt-in to certain financial incentive programs we may offer related to the collection, Sale, Sharing or deletion of your Personal Information;
    
* Request deletion of your Personal Information by us and our Service Providers, in some circumstances;
    
* Correct inaccurate Personal Information that we maintain about you; and
    
* Limit the use of sensitive Personal Information. Under the California laws, you can limit the use and disclosure of your sensitive Personal Information to certain purposes specified by law. We only use or disclose sensitive Personal Information for such permitted purposes, so we do not provide an opt out.

Further, California law provides Consumers with the right not to receive discriminatory treatment by a Business for the exercise of these rights regarding Personal Information.

### Personal Information, Collection, Disclosure, Sale and Sharing

In the past twelve months since this notice was last updated, we may have collected the following categories of information about you directly or indirectly from you or our affiliates through your use of the DJI Products and Services:

* Identifiers, such as your name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, internet protocol address, email address, account name. We collect such information (1) directly from you, e.g., forms you complete or products and services you purchase, (2) indirectly from you, e.g., from observing your actions on our website or from your devices, or (3) directly from our affiliates. We use such information for our business purposes, including specifically:  
      
    (1) Auditing related to a current interaction with the Consumer and concurrent transactions, including, but not limited to, counting ad impressions to unique visitors, verifying positioning and quality of ad impressions, and auditing compliance with this specification and other standards.  
      
    (2) Detecting security incidents, protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, and prosecuting those responsible for that activity.  
      
    (3) Debugging to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.  
      
    (4) Short-term, transient use, provided that the Personal Information is not disclosed to another third party and is not used to build a profile about a Consumer or otherwise alter an individual Consumer’s experience outside the current interaction, including, but not limited to, the contextual customization of ads shown as part of the same interaction.  
      
    (5) Performing services on behalf of the Business or Service Provider, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying customer information, processing payments, providing financing, providing advertising or marketing services, providing analytic services, or providing similar services on behalf of the Business or Service Provider.  
      
    (6) Undertaking internal research for technological development and demonstration.  
      
    (7) Undertaking activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of a service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by the Business, and to improve, upgrade, or enhance the service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by the Business.  
      
    In the past twelve months, we may have disclosed such information to:  
    ▪️ Data analytics providers.  
    ▪️ Vendors and Service Providers.  
    ▪️ Social networks.  
    ▪️ Third parties integrated into our services.  
    ▪️ Third parties as required by law and similar disclosures.  
    ▪️ Affiliates.  
    ▪️ Third parties in connection with a merger, sale, or asset transfer.  
    ▪️ Other third parties for whom we have obtained your permission to disclose your Personal Information.
    
* Categories of Personal Information in Cal. Civ. Code Section 1798.80(e),  
    such as your name, address, telephone number, education, employment, employment history, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information. We collect such information (1) directly from you, e.g., forms you complete or products and services you purchase, or (2) directly from our affiliates. We use such information for our business purposes, including specifically:  
      
    (1) Detecting security incidents, protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, and prosecuting those responsible for that activity.  
    (2) Performing services on behalf of the Business or Service Provider, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying customer information, processing payments, providing financing, providing analytic services, or providing similar services on behalf of the Business or Service Provider.  
    (3) Undertaking activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of a service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by the Business, and to improve, upgrade, or enhance the service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by the Business.  
    (4) If you are applying for a position at DJI, we may use your information for the purposes of recruiting talents for us or our affiliates.  
      
    In the past twelve months, we may have disclosed such information to:  
    ▪️ Data analytics providers.  
    ▪️ Vendors and Service Providers.  
    ▪️ Social networks.  
    ▪️ Third parties integrated into our services.  
    ▪️ Third parties as required by law and similar disclosures.  
    ▪️ Affiliates.  
      
    ▪️ Third parties in connection with a merger, sale, or asset transfer.  
    ▪️ Other third parties for whom we have obtained your permission to disclose your Personal Information.
    
* Characteristics of Protected Classifications under California or Federal Law, such as gender. We collect such information (1) directly from you, e.g., forms you complete, or (2) directly from our affiliates. We use such information for our business purposes, including specifically:  
      
    (1) Showing your user profile with information you voluntarily provided to us by submitting online forms;  
    (2) Recruiting talents for us or our affiliates.  
      
    In the past twelve months, we may have disclosed such information to:  
    ▪️ Data analytics providers.  
    ▪️ Vendors and Service Providers.  
    ▪️ Social networks.  
    ▪️ Third parties integrated into our services.  
    ▪️ Third parties as required by law and similar disclosures.  
    ▪️ Affiliates.  
    ▪️ Third parties in connection with a merger, sale, or asset transfer.  
    ▪️ Other third parties for whom we have obtained your permission to disclose your Personal Information.
    
* Commercial Information, such as records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies. We collect such information (1) directly from you, e.g., forms you complete or products and services you purchase, (2) indirectly from you, e.g., from observing your actions on our website or from your devices, or (3) directly from our affiliates. We use such information for our business purposes, including specifically:  
      
    (1) Auditing related to a current interaction with the Consumer and concurrent transactions, including, but not limited to, verifying quality of customer services, and auditing compliance with product specifications and other standards.  
    (2) Detecting security incidents, protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, and prosecuting those responsible for that activity.  
    (3) Debugging to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.  
    (4) Short-term, transient use, provided that the Personal Information is not disclosed to another third party and is not used to build a profile about a Consumer or otherwise alter an individual Consumer’s experience outside the current interaction, including, but not limited to, locating past service history.  
    (5) Performing services on behalf of the Business or Service Provider, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying customer information, processing payments, providing financing, providing advertising or marketing services, providing analytic services, or providing similar services on behalf of the Business or Service Provider.  
    (6) Undertaking internal research for technological development and demonstration.  
    (7) Undertaking activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of a service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by the Business, and to improve, upgrade, or enhance the service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by the Business.  
      
    In the past twelve months, we may have disclosed such information to:  
    ▪️ Data analytics providers.  
    ▪️ Vendors and Service Providers.  
    ▪️ Social networks.  
    ▪️ Third parties integrated into our services.  
    ▪️ Third parties as required by law and similar disclosures.  
    ▪️ Affiliates.  
    ▪️ Third parties in connection with a merger, sale, or asset transfer.  
    ▪️ Other third parties for whom we have obtained your permission to disclose your Personal Information.
    
* Internet or Other Electronic Network Activity Information, such as browsing history, search history, and information regarding a Consumer’s interaction with an internet website, application or advertisement. We collect such information (1) directly from you, e.g., forms you complete or products and services you purchase, (2) indirectly from you, e.g., from observing your actions on our website or from your devices, or (3) directly from our affiliates. We use such information for our business purposes, including specifically:  
    (1) Auditing related to a current interaction with the Consumer and concurrent transactions, including, but not limited to, counting ad impressions to unique visitors, verifying positioning and quality of ad impressions, and auditing compliance with this specification and other standards.  
    (2) Detecting security incidents, protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, and prosecuting those responsible for that activity.  
    (3) Debugging to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.  
    (4) Performing services on behalf of the Business or Service Provider, including verifying customer information, providing advertising or marketing services, providing analytic services, or providing similar services on behalf of the Business or Service Provider.  
    (5) Undertaking internal research for technological development and demonstration.  
    (6) Undertaking activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of a service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by the Business, and to improve, upgrade, or enhance the service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by the Business.  
      
    In the past twelve months, we may have disclosed such information to:  
    ▪️ Data analytics providers.  
    ▪️ Vendors and Service Providers.  
    ▪️ Social networks.  
    ▪️ Third parties integrated into our services.  
    ▪️ Third parties as required by law and similar disclosures.  
    ▪️ Affiliates.  
    ▪️ Third parties in connection with a merger, sale, or asset transfer.  
    ▪️ Other third parties for whom we have obtained your permission to disclose your Personal Information.
    
* Geolocation Data, such as precise physical location and approximate location. We collect such information (1) directly from you, e.g., products and services you purchase, (2) indirectly from you, e.g., from observing your actions on our website or from your devices. We use such information for our business purposes, including specifically:  
      
    (1) Performing services on behalf of the Business, including providing you with map services and UAS safety/regulatory notifications, finding your lost DJI Products, unlocking geofencing features in designated areas, and providing customer services.  
    (2) Debugging to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.  
    (3) Undertaking activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of a service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by the Business, and to improve, upgrade, or enhance the service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by the Business, including retaining records relating to your geofencing unlock decisions.  
      
    In the past twelve months, we may have disclosed such information to:  
    ▪️ Data analytics providers.  
    ▪️ Vendors and Service Providers.  
    ▪️ Social networks.  
    ▪️ Third parties integrated into our services.  
    ▪️ Third parties as required by law and similar disclosures.  
    ▪️ Affiliates.  
    ▪️ Third parties in connection with a merger, sale, or asset transfer.  
    ▪️ Other third parties for whom we have obtained your permission to disclose your Personal Information.
    
* Sensory Information, such as audio, electronic, visual, thermal, or similar information. We collect such information directly from you, e.g., products and services you purchase. We use such information for our business purposes, including specifically, performing services on behalf of the Business or Service Provider, including providing customer service.  
      
    In the past twelve months, we may have disclosed such information to:  
    ▪️ Affiliates.  
    ▪️ Third parties as required by law and similar disclosures.  
    ▪️ Third parties in connection with a merger, sale, or asset transfer.
    
* Professional or employment-related information, such as job application or resume information, past and current job history, and job performance information, unless exempt. We collect such information directly from you, e.g., forms you complete or products and services you purchase. We use such information for our business purposes, including specifically, recruiting talents for us or our affiliates.  
      
    In the past twelve months, we may have disclosed such information to:  
    ▪️ Affiliates.  
    ▪️ Third parties as required by law and similar disclosures.  
    ▪️ Third parties in connection with a merger, sale, or asset transfer.
    
* Inferences Drawn from Personal Information, such as Consumer profiles reflecting a Consumer’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, preferences, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes. We collect such information indirectly from you, e.g., from observing your actions on our website or from your devices. We use such information for our business purposes, including specifically:  
      
    (1) Auditing related to a current interaction with the Consumer and concurrent transactions, including, but not limited to, counting ad impressions to unique visitors, verifying positioning and quality of ad impressions, and auditing compliance with this specification and other standards.  
    (2) Detecting security incidents, protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, and prosecuting those responsible for that activity.  
    (3) Debugging to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.  
    (4) Undertaking internal research for technological development and demonstration.  
    (5) Undertaking activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of a service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by the Business, and to improve, upgrade, or enhance the service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by the Business.  
      
    In the past twelve months, we may have disclosed such information to:  
    ▪️ Data analytics providers.  
    ▪️ Affiliates.  
    ▪️ Third parties integrated into our services.  
    ▪️ Third parties as required by law and similar disclosures.  
    ▪️ Third parties in connection with a merger, sale, or asset transfer.
    
* Sensitive Personal Information: account log-in and precise geolocation data. We collect such information directly from you, e.g., from your account registration, or indirectly from you, e.g., from your device. We use such information for our business purposes, including specifically:  
    ▪️ Performing services on behalf of the Business.  
    ▪️ Helping to ensure security and integrity to the extent the use of the Consumer’s Personal Information is reasonably necessary and proportionate for these purposes.  
      
    In the past twelve months, we may have disclosed such information to:  
    ▪️ Vendors and Service Providers.

Such information may be used for the purposes for which it was collected or as otherwise permitted or required by applicable law.  
  
We have not sold or shared your personal information in the preceding twelve months from the date of last review of this Privacy Policy, do not currently sell or share, and will not sell or share your personal information for twelve months from the date of the last review of this Privacy Policy.

### Requests

You can make requests related to your California privacy rights at the attached [link](https://www.dji.com/nz/policy/ccpa-contact-form). You may also make those requests by email to [support@privacy.dji.com](mailto:support@privacy.dji.com) or in writing to SZ DJI Technology Co., Ltd., 14th Floor, West Wing, Skyworth Semiconductor Design Building, No.18 Gaoxin South 4th Ave, Nanshan District, Shenzhen, China, 518057. Please be aware that we do not accept or process requests through other means (e.g., via fax or social media).  
  
We will review the information provided and may request additional information to ensure we are interacting with the correct individual. If you have an online account with us, you may be required to log-in to your account for identity verification. If you do not have an account with us, additional information to verify your identity may be required by law before we may take action upon such a request. This additional information may vary depending on the nature of your request and/or the nature of the information about which your request relates. In some cases, we may also be required by law to obtain a signed declaration under penalty of perjury from you that you are the subject of the request being made. If we suspect fraudulent or malicious activity on or from your account, we will delay taking action on your request until we can appropriately verify your identity and the request as authentic.  
  
By law, we are not required to collect Personal Information that we otherwise would not collect in the ordinary course of our business, retain Personal Information for longer than we would otherwise retain such information in the ordinary course of our business, or re-identify or otherwise link information that is not maintained in a manner that would be considered Personal Information. If we have not requested specific additional information from you to verify your request, please do not send such information.  
  
We generally will aim to avoid requesting additional information from you for the purposes of verification. However, if we cannot reasonably verify your identity or more information is needed for security or fraud-prevention purposes, we may consider any of the following factors, alone or in combination, in requesting additional information:

* The type, sensitivity, and value of the Personal Information collected and maintained about the Consumer, as applicable law requires a more stringent verification process for sensitive or valuable Personal Information;
    
* The risk of harm to the Consumer posed by any unauthorized access or deletion;
    
* The likelihood that fraudulent or malicious actors would seek the Personal Information;
    
* Whether the Personal Information to be provided by the Consumer to verify their identity is sufficiently robust to protect against fraudulent requests or being spoofed or fabricated;
    
* The manner in which the Business interacts with the Consumer;
    
* Available technology for verification; and
    
* Other factors that may be reasonable in the circumstances, are consistent with industry practice, are recommended by California government officials, or which may be required by law or regulation following the effective date of this Privacy Policy.

If your request is regarding household information, the same verification steps above are required before we can provide you with aggregate household information. For us to process a request for access to or deletion of specific pieces of information regarding your household, all members of the household must make the request, and we must be able to verify each household member.  
  
In some cases, we may not have sufficient information about you or your household to be able to verify your identity or sufficiently differentiate you from another Consumer or household to the degree of certainty required by law, in which case, we will not be able to act upon your request. In such cases, it may be unlikely that we would be able to identify you or your household in the future without collecting significantly more information or seeking to re-identify de-identified information. At this time, we do not intend to take such steps in response to a request made pursuant to this Privacy Policy and applicable law does not require that we do so. If, in the future, we determine a reasonable method to identify you or your household absent such steps, we will provide an update to you through this Privacy Policy and in response to any such request at that time.  
  
Information that you submit for the purpose of allowing us to verify your identity in furtherance of a Consumer-related or household-related request pursuant to California law will only be used by us, and our Service Providers if any, for that purpose and no other. Except where we are required by law to maintain such information for record-keeping purposes, we will take steps to delete any new Personal Information collected for the purpose of verification as soon as practical after processing your request.  
  
Please also be aware that making any such request does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal or deletion of Personal Information or content you may have posted, and there may be circumstances in which the law does not require or allow us to fulfill your request, including, for example, where fulfilling your request may infringe upon the rights and freedoms of other Consumers.  
  
We reserve the right to charge a reasonable fee or take other appropriate action in response to requests from a Consumer or household that are manifestly unfounded or excessive, in particular because of their repetitive character.  
  
You may designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf pursuant to applicable law. We accept documentation of your designation in the form of a valid power of attorney and/or a notarized statement. You must submit evidence of your designation of an authorized agent in writing to: SZ DJI Technology Co., Ltd.14th Floor, West Wing, Skyworth Semiconductor Design Building, No.18 Gaoxin South 4th Ave, Nanshan District, Shenzhen, China, 518057. We may require verification of your authorized agent in addition to the information for verification above for Consumers and households.

### Do Not Track

DJI does not currently take steps to respond to browsers’ “Do Not Track” signals as no uniform standard to respond to such signals has been developed at this time.

### Deidentified Information

Where we maintain or use deidentified information, we will continue to maintain and use the deidentified information only in a deidentified fashion and will not attempt to re-identify the information.

### Notice of Financial Incentive

With regard to our education discount program, we offer financial incentives to Consumers based upon the retention of sale of a Consumer’s Personal Information calculated based on a good-faith estimate of the value of the Consumer’s data, which forms the basis for offering such financial incentives. The financial incentive offered is a discount on the price of some DJI Products and Services, based on affiliation with an employer group or educational institution with which we partner. The categories of Personal Information that are implicated by the financial incentive or price or service difference include your place of employment or educational institution. You may choose to provide an email address associated with your employer or educational institution, which we will validate manually.  
  
The method we use to calculate the value of a Consumer’s data is that our calculation used in good-faith of the likelihood of increased sales of DJI Products and Services to Consumers at your place of employment or educational institution.  
  
You may enroll in or withdraw from our financial incentive program at any time by updating your preferences by email at [support@privacy.dji.com](mailto:support@privacy.dji.com), or in writing at SZ DJI Technology Co., Ltd.14th Floor, West Wing, Skyworth Semiconductor Design Building, No.18 Gaoxin South 4th Ave, Nanshan District, Shenzhen, China, 518057.

### Questions

For questions regarding this California Privacy Notice, contact us by email at [support@privacy.dji.com](mailto:support@privacy.dji.com), or in writing at SZ DJI Technology Co., Ltd.14th Floor, West Wing, Skyworth Semiconductor Design Building, No.18 Gaoxin South 4th Ave, Nanshan District, Shenzhen, China, 518057.

Shop with DJI Store

Get 1% DJI Credit Rewards, Free Shipping on Orders Over USD $149, 14-Day Returns, and other exclusive official offers.

### Thanks for signing up!

Thank you for your attention and support of DJI.

Login or register at [Store.dji.com](https://store.dji.com/?utm_source=official&utm_medium=subscribe&utm_campaign=subscribe_exp) with your subscription email to view your coupon.

Close

### Subscribe

### Subscribe

Be the first to receive our latest product updates, newest offerings, and free product trials.

Subscribe to get exclusive offer, then login or register at [Store.dji.com](https://store.dji.com/?utm_source=official&utm_medium=subscribe&utm_campaign=subscribe_description) with your subscription email to check it.

Subscribe

Please enter a valid email address

You can learn more about how we handle user data through the [DJI Privacy Policy](https://www.dji.com/uk/policy).

Product Categories

Service Plans

Where to Buy

Cooperation

Fly Safe

Support

Explore

Community

Subscribe

Subscribe

Get the latest news from DJI

Subscribe to get exclusive offer, then login or register at [Store.dji.com](https://store.dji.com/?utm_source=official&utm_medium=subscribe&utm_campaign=subscribe_description) with your subscription email to check it.

Have questions? Get help from a DJI expert.

### Select Your Country/Region

Asia Pacific

* 中国大陆简体中文* 中國香港繁體中文* Hong Kong, ChinaEnglish* IndonesiaEnglish* 日本日本語* 中國澳門繁體中文* SingaporeEnglish* 대한민국한국어* 中國台灣繁體中文* AustraliaEnglish* New ZealandEnglish

Europe

* ÖsterreichDeutsch* РоссияPусский* BelgiumEnglish* BulgariaEnglish* CroatiaEnglish* Czech RepublicEnglish* DenmarkEnglish* EstoniaEnglish* FinlandEnglish* FranceFrançais* DeutschlandDeutsch* GreeceEnglish* HungaryEnglish* IrelandEnglish* ItaliaItaliano* LatviaEnglish* LiechtensteinDeutsch* LithuaniaEnglish* LuxembourgFrançais* MaltaEnglish* MonacoFrançais* NetherlandsEnglish* NorwayEnglish* PolandEnglish* PortugalEnglish* SlovakiaEnglish* SloveniaEnglish* EspañaEspañol* SwedenEnglish* SwitzerlandEnglish* United KingdomEnglish

Middle East

* UAEEnglish

North America

* CanadaEnglish* CanadaFrançais* Puerto RicoEnglish* United StatesEnglish* MéxicoEspañol

South America

* BrasilPortuguês (BR)

Other Countries and Regions

* Other RegionsEnglish

United Kingdom / English

Copyright © 2024 DJI All Rights Reserved.
